简单地单击就能让你的程序运行在模拟器上，
The simplicity of hitting run and having your app appear on an emulator,
这其中隐藏了很多复杂的细节。别忘了，Android系统由多个层次组成
hides a lot of complexity. Remember that Android is a full software stack.
Adspace 是 Linux 内核，
Adspace is a Linux Kernel,
负责底层任务，像是硬件总线和面板管理
which handles low level tasks like hardware fibers and panel management.
在它上面是C/C++核心库，例如 Libsc SQLite
On top of that, are some core C and C plus plus libraries like Libsc and
和 Android Runtime。 这里面包含一些很酷的库
SQLite and the Android Runtime. That includes cool Android libraries and
和Android的虚拟机，Dalvik或者最近出的ART
the Android virtual machines, Dalvik or more recently ART. Your apps run
你的App在它自己的虚拟机实例上运行
within its own instance of the VM using the classes and services provided here
使用着应用程序框架提供的类和服务  在这些的上面 是应用程序层
in the application framework. On top of that, sits the application layer,
包含你的应用程序和其他所有装在这个设备上应用
which includes your app and every other app that's installed on the device. So,
所以 当你在Android Studio点击运行你的程序时 首先是
when you hit Run in Android Studio, the first thing that happens is your code
你的代码会被编译成字节码 这样就可以在Android虚拟机上运行了
gets compiled into byte code that can be run in the Android Virtual Machine.
然后这个字节码会被安装到设备上
That then gets installed onto the device. In Android Studio,
Android Studio使用gradle来帮你做这些 例如管理依赖关系
this is done using gradle, a build tool kit that manages dependencies and
你也可以自定义gradle的编译配置
allows you to define custom build logic.
你可以选择 Make Project 来手动地开始gradle编译
You can manually start a gradle build in the IDE by selecting make project.
也可以选择编译菜单中的 Make Project
You can also do this by going to the build menu and selecting make project from
你可以用gradle控制台看看有没有日志或者编译错误
there, or you can use the gradle console to observe any logs or
还可以打开gradle任务窗口看看有哪些任务
build errors, or open the gradle tasks window to see any available tasks.
双击他们就能执行 也可以用命令行执行
Double clicking on any of them will execute it. This will work from
当你进入你的项目的根目录时
the command line too. Once you've navigated to the root of your project folder,
可以用 ./gradlew tasks 查看所有能运行的任务
you can run gradlew tasks to see all the tasks that you can run. You can learn
你可以看看笔记里的链接学习到更多关于gradle的知识
more about gradle by checking out the links in the instructor notes. For now,
现在我们首先建立一个Android项目 随后gradle会
note that we start with the project, which gradle then builds and
将字节码和其他资源（如图片、字符串、UI的XML文件）
then packages the byte code along with the external resources such as images,
一起编译打包到一个APK应用程序包里
strings, and uixml into an application package. This is called an APK, and
APK包其实是一个特殊格式的zip文件 当准备好APK包后
it's a specially formatted zip file. Once you've got your APK ready to go,
给它签上名 然后通过Android Debug Bridge（ADB）推送到设备上
it's signed and then pushed to the device using the Android Debug Bridge or
我们可以通过终端界面用ADB和设备交互、debug
ADB. If we return to the terminal, you can see that ADB lets you interact and
物理的设备和虚拟设备都可以  还可以做例如推进、拉出文件
debug apps on any device, physical or virtual. Things like pushing and
查看logcat输出
pulling files, viewing logcat output, or
甚至运行一个远程的shell 一旦Android的GDO被ADB安装了APK
even running a remote shell. So once Android's GDO has ADB installed the APK,
它会再次用ADB发送一个命令 通过远程shell来启动这个App
it uses ADB again to launch the app by sending a stock command via the remote
命令中包含你的主Activity的包名和类名
shell, by identifying the package and class name of your main activity.